{
    "subject": "Peter_Gilmore",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jan_Waters",
    "human_readable": "Peter Gilmore is married to Jan Waters.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9808722734451294,
            "question": "Are Peter Gilmore and Jan Waters in a marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.953390896320343,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Peter Gilmore and Jan Waters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8625777363777161,
            "question": "Who is married to Jan Waters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8472451567649841,
            "question": "Is Peter Gilmore married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8420296311378479,
            "question": "To whom is Peter Gilmore married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7709047198295593,
            "question": "Name the husband of Jan Waters."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7310001254081726,
            "question": "Who is connected to Jan Waters through marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7151795029640198,
            "question": "Who is Peter Gilmore's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6465994119644165,
            "question": "What is the name of Jan Waters' spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34968477487564087,
            "question": "What is the name of Peter Gilmore's partner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter Gilmore is married to Jan Waters.",
            "html": "yago_25039_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jan Waters' spouse?",
            "html": "yago_25039_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Peter Gilmore's wife?",
            "html": "yago_25039_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is connected to Jan Waters through marriage?",
            "html": "yago_25039_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25039_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Jan Waters was once married to actor Peter Gilmore, and also provide details about their marriage and Peter's subsequent marriages to Una Stubbs and Anne Stallybrass."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"He was first married to actress Jan Waters,\" which supports the triple stating \"Peter Gilmore is married to Jan Waters.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}